RG 071, Department of Housing
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Deputy Commissioner, 1978-1990; 38 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - Victor Cruse, 1981-1986; 12 cubic feet
      - T003128, 11 cubic feet
        - Tornado disaster (Box 20)
        - Travel milage (Box 20)
        - Treasurer's Office (Box 20)
        - Tri-state regional planning (Box 20)
        - United Technologies (Box 20)
        - United Way, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Updike, Kelly and Spellacy (Box 20)
        - Upper Albany Housing Development Corporation, 3 folders (entire box) (Box 21)
        - Upward Mobility program (Box 21)
        - Urban Homeless (Box 21)
        - Urban Homesteading loan fund (Box 22)
        - Urban Institute (Box 22)
        - Urban renewal (Box 22)
        - U.S. Systems Corporation (Box 22)
        - UtilityDevelopment Corporation (Box 22)
        - Vernon Street Bus Garage (Box 22)
        - Vernon Street property (Box 22)
        - Vine Street, 95 (Box 22)
        - Waterbury, Fairmont Heights (Box 22)
        - Waterbury, Authority of the City of (Box 22)
        - Waterbury HSD/HDC (Box 22)
        - White House Conference on the Aging (Box 22)
        - White House Economic Recovery plan (Box 22)
        - White House on Children, Governor (Box 22)
        - Workshops, DOH (Box 22)
        - Workshops, Strategy planning (Box 22)
        - Yankee Mac (Box 22)
        - Yerwood (Box 22)
        - Zion Park (Box 22)
      - 1991-020, 1 cubic foot
        - Housing and black aged (Box 6)
        - Capitol Housing, 1986 (Box 6)
        - VRC, 1986 (Box 6)
        - Victor R. Cruse (Box 6)
          - Correspondence (Box 6)
          - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 6)
          - Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Yasha M. Escalera, 1987-1988; 5 cubic feet; 1991-020
      - Unarranged (Box 7)
      - Unarranged (Box 8)
      - Agendas, Supervisor's Meetings (Box 9)
      - Director's meetings (Box 9)
      - Commissioner's meetings (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder (Box 9)
      - Regulations, Draft, 1987 (Box 9)
      - Reorganization Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      - Uniform Relocation Assistance Act (Box 9)
      - Urban Homesteading (Box 9)
      - Weatherization/Conservation, Demo. Program (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 July (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 August (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 September (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 October (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 November (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 December (Box 9)
      - The Emmaus Institute (Box 9)
      - DOH audit (Box 9)
      - Three year housing advisory plan, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Action plan to address the needs of the homeless, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Supervisor's meetings, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Out-going, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Illegable (Box 9)
      - In-coming, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Memos from Pat (Box 9)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, In-coming (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 January (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 April (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 May (Box 9)
      - Untitled folder, 1987 June (Box 9)
      - Affirmative action (Box 10)
      - Agency objectives, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
      - Biographies, Reorganization (Box 10)
      - Budget options, 1987 (Box 10)
      - Budget options, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Housing, Investment fund (Box 10)
      - CO-OP Intiatives project, Sarah Page (Box 10)
      - Connecticut plan (Box 10)
      - Correspondence (Box 10)
        - In-coming (Box 10)
        - Out-going (Box 10)
      - Correspondence, Governor's office, To/from (Box 10)
      - DOH, Mission and goals (Box 10)
      - ECHO program, Employer Assisted housing (Box 10)
      - Insurance coverage (Box 10)
      - L"Ambiance plaza (Box 10)
      - LEC/MHA regulations (Box 10)
      - Leg. Appeals (Box 10)
      - Legislative Inquiry (Box 10)
      - Legislative Inquiry, External (Box 10)
      - Legislative summary, 1988 (Box 10)
      - Manchester housing needs (Box 10)
      - Untitled folder (Box 10)
      - Media interviews (Box 10)
      - Untitled folder (Box 10)
      - New Haven (Box 10)
        - Handicapped (Box 10)
        - Homelessness (Box 10)
      - Metropolitan insurance (Box 11)
      - Directorio Hispano (Box 11)
      - United Way, 2 Folders (Box 11)
      - San Juan Center (Box 11)
      - Unarranged materials, 4 inches (Box 11)
      - Yasha Escalera, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - CBT. Adv. Board (Box 11)
      - Yasha Escalera, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - GHBDC (Box 11)
      - Harford Foundation for Public Giving (Box 11)
- Series 3. Department of Community Affairs, 1943-1980; 32.5 cubic feet
  - Block Grants, 1958-1978; 22.5 cubic feet
    - 1985-026A, 11 cubic feet
      - Correspondence
        - Ansonia, MR-29, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - Bristol, MR-21, 21A, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - Danbury, MR-22, 22A, 41, 57, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - Darien, MR-36, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - Derby, MR-39, 53, 62, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - East Hartford, MR-23, 23A, 58, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 1)
        - Enfield, MR-26, 56, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 3)
        - Greenwich, MR-9, 32, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 2)
        - Hartford, MR-3, 3A, 17, 30, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 2)
        - Hartford Reference, Salary Increase Studt (Box 2)
        - Hartford, Quarterly Reports, 1950-1960; 2 folders (Box 2)
        - Meriden, MR-5, 24, 52, 1961-1965; 6 folders (Box 3)
        - Middletown, MR-11, 11A, 47, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 3)
        - Milford, MR-20, 72, 72E, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 3)
        - Naugatuck, MR-15, 15A, 43, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 3)
        - New Britain, MR-12, 12E, 45, 64, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 4)
        - New Canaan, MR-37, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 4)
        - New Hartford, MR-38, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 4)
        - New Haven, MR-2, 35, 65, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 4)
        - New London, MR-25, 48, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 4)
        - Norwalk, MR-27, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Norwich (city), MR-18, 18A, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Norwich (town), MR-4, 4A, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Putnam, MR-16, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Seymour, MR-19, 19A, 66, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Shelton, MR-13, 51, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Southington, MR-14, 14E, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 5)
        - Stamford, MR-6, 33, 55, 68, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 6)
        - Southington, MR-14, 14E, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 6)
        - Stratford, MR-71, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 6)
        - Torrington, MR-67, 1956-1966; 11 folders (Box 6)
        - Torrington, MR-E-1, 1958-1960; 3 folders (Box 6)
        - Wallingford, MR-8, 8A, 46, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 6)
        - Waterbury, MR-10, 31, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 7)
        - Westport, MR-28, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 7)
        - Wethersfield, MR-1, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 7)
        - Willimantic, MR-7, 34, 50, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 7)
        - Winchester, MR-63, 1961-1966; 6 folders (Box 7)
      - Development Correspondence
        - Danbury, E-2, 1958-1966 (Box 8)
        - Derby, E-11, 1961-1967 (Box 8)
        - East Hartford, E-6, 1959-1964 (Box 8)
        - Enfield, E-31, 1965-1968 (Box 8)
        - Enfield, E-10, 1961-1965 (Box 8)
        - Enfield, E-21, 1962-1966 (Box 8)
        - Meriden, E-7, 1959-1965 (Box 8)
        - Naugatuck, E-12, 1962-1965 (Box 8)
        - New London, E-9, 1960-1965; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Putnam, E-4, 1960-1964 (Box 8)
        - Putnam, E-26, 1964-1967 (Box 8)
        - Putnam, E-4, 26, Misc., 1959-1967 (Box 8)
      - Advances
        - Danbury, E-2, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
        - Derby, E-11, 1962-1965 (Box 9)
        - East Hartford, E-6, 1960-1964 (Box 9)
        - Enfield, E-10, 1962-1963 (Box 9)
        - Enfield, E-21 (Box 9)
        - Enfield, E-31, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
        - Meriden, E-7, 1961-1964 (Box 9)
        - Naugatuck, 1962-1964 (Box 9)
        - New Britain, E-3, 1961-1962 (Box 9)
        - New London, E-9, 1962-1964 (Box 9)
        - Putnam, E-4, 1961-1963 (Box 9)
        - Putnam, E-26, 1964-1966 (Box 9)
        - Stratford, E-5, 1960-1963 (Box 9)
      - Quarterly Reports
        - Ansonia, MR-29, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Bridgeport, MR-40, 40E, 44, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Bristol, MR-21, 21A, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Danbury, MR22, 22A, 41, 57, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Darien, MR-36, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Derby, MR-39, 53, 62, 1961 (Box 10)
        - East Hartford, MR-23, 23A, 68, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Emfield, MR-26, 56, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Greenwich, MR-9, 32, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Hartford, MR-3, 3A, 17, 30, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Meriden, MR-5, 24, 52, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Middletown, MR-11, 11A, 47, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Milford, MR-20, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Naugatuck, MR-15, 15A, 43, 49, 61, 1961 (Box 10)
        - New Britain, MR-45, 64, 1961 (Box 10)
        - New Hartford, MR-38, 1961 (Box 10)
        - New Haven, MR-2, 35, 65, 1961 (Box 10)
        - New London, MR-25, 48, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Norwalk, MR-27, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Norwich (city), MR-18, 18A, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Norwich (town), MR-4, 4A, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Putnam, MR-16, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Seymour, MR-19, 19A, 66, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Shelton, MR-13, 51, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Southington, MR-14, 14E, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Stamford, MR-6, 33, 55, 68, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Stratford, MR-71, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Torrington, MR-67, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Wallingford, MR-8, 8A, 46, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Waterbury, MR-10, 31, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Westport, MR-28, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Wethersfield, MR-1, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Willimantic, MR-7, 34, 50, 1961 (Box 10)
        - Winchester, MR-63, 1961 (Box 10)
    - 1986-010B, 4 cubic feet
      - Bid Documents (Box 1)
        - Hamden, E-82 (Box 1)
        - Killingly, E-83 (Box 1)
        - Southington, E-84 (Box 1)
        - Thompson, E-85 (Box 1)
        - Woodstock, E-88 (Box 1)
        - Guilford, E-90 (Box 1)
        - Plainfield, E-91 (Box 1)
        - East Haven, E-93 (Box 1)
        - Farmington, E-94 (Box 1)
        - Litchfield, E-95 (Box 1)
        - Naugatuck, E-96 (Box 1)
        - North Canaan, E-97 (Box 1)
        - Plymouth, E-98 (Box 1)
        - Simsbury, E-99 (Box 1)
        - Somers, E-102 (Box 1)
        - Newington, E-104 (Box 1)
      - Maintenance Files (Box 2)
        - Stamford, MR-33, William C. Ward Homes (Box 2)
        - Derby, MR-39, Lakeview (Box 2)
        - Naugatuck, MR-43, Lewis Meadows Ext. (Box 2)
        - Naugatuck, MR-43, Lewis City Heights (Box 2)
        - Derby, MR-53, McLaughlin Terrace (Box 2)
        - New Haven, MR-65, Budget Cost Estimate (Box 2)
        - Winchester, MR-63, Ramsay Heights (Box 2)
        - Stamford, MR-68 (Box 2)
      - Contracts
        - Wethersfield, MR-1, Highvue (Box 3)
        - New Haven, MR-2, McConaughy Terrace (Box 3)
        - Hartford, MR-3, Rice Heights (Box 3)
        - Hartford, MR-3A, Rice Heights Extension (Box 3)
        - Norwich, MR-4, Melrose Park (Box 3)
        - Norwich, MR-4A, Sunset Park (Box 3)
        - Meriden, MR-5, Johnson Farms (Box 3)
        - Stamford, MR-6, Oak Park (Box 3)
        - Willimantic, MR-7, Terry Court (Box 3)
        - Wallingford, MR-8, Backes Court (Box 3)
        - Wallingford, MR-8A, Ulrich Heights (Box 3)
        - Greenwich, MR-9, Adams Gardens (Box 3)
        - Waterbury, MR-10, Fairmount Heights (Box 3)
        - Middletown, MR-11, Sunset Ridge (Box 3)
        - Middletown, MR-11A, Sunset Ridge (Box 3)
        - Middletown, MR-11 EXT (Box 3)
        - New Britain, MR-12, Corbin Heights (Box 3)
        - New Britain, MR-12A, Corbin Heights (Box 3)
        - Shelton, MR-13, Sunnyside (Box 3)
        - Southington, MR-14, Mt. View Terrace (Box 3)
        - Naugatuck, MR-15, Naugawam Village (Box 3)
        - Naugatuck, MR-15A, Lewis Meadows (Box 3)
        - Putnam, MR-16, World War II Memorial Terrace (Box 3)
        - Hartford, MR-17, Chester Bowles Park (Box 3)
        - Norwich, MR-18, Fairview Heights (Box 3)
        - Norwich, MR-18A, Hillside Terrace (Box 3)
        - Seymour, MR-19A, Castle Heights (Box 3)
        - Seymour, MR-19, Smith Acres (Box 3)
        - Milford, MR-20, Peter Prudder Village (Box 3)
        - Bristol, MR-21, Dutton Heights (Box 3)
        - Bristol, MR-21A, Zbikowski Park (Box 3)
        - Danbury, MR-22, Fairfield Ridge (Box 3)
        - East Hartford, MR-23A, Veteran's Terrace (Box 3)
        - Danbury, MR-22A, Mill Ridge (Box 3)
        - East Hartford, MR-23, King Court (Box 3)
        - Meriden, MR-24, Yale Acres (Box 3)
        - New London, MR-25, Briarcliff (Box 3)
        - Enfield, MR-26, Green Valley Village (Box 3)
        - Norwalk, MR-27, Colonial Village (Box 3)
        - Westport, MR-28, Hales Court (Box 3)
        - Ansonia, MR-29, Webb Terrace (Box 3)
        - Hartford, MR-30, Westbrook Village (Box 3)
        - Waterbury, MR-31, Broadview Acres (Box 3)
        - Glastonbury, E-62 (Box 4)
        - Waterbury, MR-31, Broadview Acres (Box 4)
        - Greenwich, MR-32, Hamilton Court (Box 4)
        - Stamford, MR-33, Stamford Heights (Box 4)
        - Willimantic, MR-34, Marcella Curran Eastman Terrace (Box 4)
        - New Haven, MR-35, Brookside (Box 4)
        - Darien, MR-36, Allen O'Niel Houses (Box 4)
        - Neew Canaan, MR-37, Mill Apartments (Box 4)
        - New Hartford, MR-38, Loomis Heights (Box 4)
        - Bridgeport, MR-40 (Box 4)
        - Bridgeport, MR-40 Ext (Box 4)
        - Danbury, MR-41 (Box 4)
        - Hartford, MR-42 (Box 4)
        - Naugatuck, MR-43 (Box 4)
        - Bridgeport, MR-44 (Box 4)
        - New Britain, MR-45 (Box 4)
        - Wallingford, MR-46 (Box 4)
        - Middletown, MR-47 (Box 4)
        - New London, MR-48 (Box 4)
        - Naugatuck, MR-49 (Box 4)
        - Willimantic, MR-50 (Box 4)
        - Shelton, MR-51 (Box 4)
        - Meriden, MR-52 (Box 4)
        - Derby, MR-53 (Box 4)
        - Stamford, MR-55 (Box 4)
        - Enfield, MR-56 (Box 4)
        - Danbury, MR-56 (Box 4)
        - East Hartford, MR-58 (Box 4)
        - Naugatuck, MR-61 (Box 4)
        - Derby, MR-62 (Box 4)
        - Winsted, MR-63 (Box 4)
        - New Britain, MR-64 (Box 4)
        - Seymour, MR-66 (Box 4)
        - Stratford, MR-71 (Box 4)
        - Bristol, MR-59, Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Waterbury, MR-60, Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Stamford, MR-55, Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Stamford, MR-68, Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Groton, MR-69, Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Stamford, MR-55, Correspondence (Box 4)
    - 1989-005, 2.5 cubic feet
      Includes adevelopment current correspondence, advances, architect, agreements.
      - Glastonbury, E-39 (Box 1)
      - Enfield, E-50 (Box 1)
      - Fairfield, E-23 (Box 1)
      - Glastonbury, E-39 (Box 1)
      - New Britain, E-25 (Box 1)
      - New Britain, E-3 (Box 1)
      - Norwich City Housing Authority, Public Act No. 600 (Box 1)
      - Norwich, E-15 (Box 1)
      - Torrington, E-1 (Box 2)
      - Torrington, Second Elderly Project (Box 2)
      - Torrington, E-14 (Box 2)
      - Torrington, E-35 (Box 2)
      - Torrington, E-73 (Box 2)
      - Somers, E-66 (Box 2)
      - Stamford, E-13 (Box 2)
      - Stamford, E-13 (Box 3)
      - Wallingford E-18 (Box 3)
      - Wallingford, E-18, 34 (Box 3)
      - Windsor Housing Authority, Elderly (Box 3)
      - Tenant Survey, Naugatuck, E-30,71 (Box 3)
      - Tenant Survey, Voluntown, E-45 (Box 3)
      - Tenant Survey, Wallingford, E-34 (Box 3)
    - 2004-025, 5 cubic feet
      - Griswold, E-42 (Box 1)
      - Guilford, E-55 (Box 1)
      - Colchester, E-44 (Box 1)
      - Groton, E-36 (Box 1)
      - Milford, E-19 (Box 2)
      - Danbury, E-16 (Box 2)
      - East Windsor, E-51 (Box 2)
      - Ellington, E-52 (Box 2)
      - Enfield, E-50 (Box 2)
      - Naugatuck, E-30 (Box 3)
      - Naugatuck, E-71 (Box 3)
      - Norwich (city), E-32 (Box 3)
      - Norwich (town), E-20 (Box 3)
      - Wallingford, E-34 (Box 3)
      - Glastonbury, E-39 (Box 3)
      - Simsbury, E-54 (Box 4)
      - Somers, E-66 (Box 4)
      - Southington, E-33 (Box 4)
      - Suffield, E-28 (Box 4)
      - Suffield, E-60 (Box 5)
      - Voluntown, E-45 (Box 5)
      - Waterbury, E-24 (Box 5)
      - Winchester, E-72 (Box 5)
      - Willimantic, E-22 (Box 1)
      - Windsor, E-43 (Box 1)
  - Pilot Programs, 1968-1972; 1989-003; 2 cubic feet
    Includes applications, agreements, contracts, and payments.
    - Bristol, 2-203 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Bristol, 2-120 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Bristol, 2-138 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Bridgeport, 5-275 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Ansonia, 5-316 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Bridgeport, 5-18 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Bridgeport, 5-42 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Ansonia, 5-170 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Ansonia, 5-202 Pilot (Box 1)
    - Pilot allocations, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - Payment in lieu of taxes, General (Box 1)
    - Danbury, 5-8 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Danbury, 5-186 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Danbury, 5-260 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Derby, 5-169 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Derby, 5-262 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Derby, 5-209 Pilot (Box 2)
    - East Hartford, 2-87 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Enfield, 2-204 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Enfield, 2-49 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Enfield, 2-129 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Greenwich, 5-210 Pilot (Box 2)
    - Greenwich, 5-116 Pilot (Box 2)
  - Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980; T003133; 8 cubic feet
    For individual maps see
    Inventory of Department of Housing Planning Maps
    .
    - Andover, 1959-1960, undated; 22 maps (Box 1)
    - Ansonia, 1956, 1965, undated; 8 maps (Box 1)
    - Avon, 1954-1957, 1969; 33 maps (Box 1)
    - Beacon Falls, 1956; 24 maps (Box 1)
    - Bethany, 1958, 1961-1962, undated; 25 maps (Box 1)
    - Bethel, 1953, 1957, undated; 24 maps (Box 1)
    - Bloomfield, 1962, 1967-1968; 10 maps (Box 2)
    - Bozrah, 1980; 1 map (Box 2)
    - Bridgeport, 1974; 2 maps (Box 2)
    - Bristol, 1974, undated; 5 maps (Box 2)
    - Brooklyn, 1968; 33 maps (Box 2)
    - Chaplin, 1967; 20 maps (Box 3)
    - Cheshire, undated; 1 fragment (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - Columbia, 1964; 1 map (Box 3)
    - Danbury, 1955-1958, 1977, undated; 46 maps (Box 3)
    - Danielson, 1960, 1963-1965, undated; 25 maps (Box 3)
    - Derby, 1957-1958, 1973-1974, undated; 13 maps (Box 3)
    - East Granby, 1955-11957; 55 maps (Box 3)
    - East Haddam, 1966-1967; 21 maps (Box 4)
    - East Hartford, 1950, 1953, undated; 3 maps (Box 4)
    - East Haven, 1958, 1974; 14 maps (Box 4)
    - East Windsor, 1966-1967, undated; 20 maps (Box 4)
    - Ellington, 1966-1967, 1971; 18 maps (Box 4)
    - Essex, 1955, 1970, undated; 27 maps (Box 4)
    - Fairfield, 1970; 1 map (Box 5)
    - Farmington, 1962, 1964, undated; 3 maps (Box 5)
    - Glastonbury, 1956, 1969-1970; 12 maps (Box 5)
    - Goshen, 1959; 2 maps (Box 5)
    - Granby, 1962-1963, undated; 14 maps (Box 5)
    - Greenwich, 1975; 2 map (Box 5)
    - Groton, 1960-1961, undated; 24 maps (Box 5)
    - Guilford, 1965, 1967, 1972; 9 maps (Box 5)
    - Haddam, 1961; 1 map (Box 5)
    - Hamden, 1950; 1 map (Box 5)
    - Hebron, 1964-1965, 1974, 1977, 1980, undated; 25 maps (Box 5)
    - Killingly, undated; 1 map (Box 5)
    - Killingworth, 1967; 11 maps (Box 5)
    - Lyme, 1964, undated; 7 maps (Box 6)
    - Manchester, 1960, 1970, 1980, undated; 10 maps (Box 6)
    - Mansfield, 1970, 1977; 12 maps (Box 6)
    - Marlborough, 1967; 1 map (Box 6)
    - Meriden, 1959, undated; 2 maps (Box 6)
    - Milford, 1962; 1 map (Box 6)
    - Monroe, undated; 1 map (Box 6)
    - New Canaan, 1950; 1 map (Box 6)
    - New Hartford, 1957, 1967; 26 maps (Box 6)
    - New Haven, 1963; 1 map (Box 6)
    - Newington, 1967; 2 maps (Box 6)
    - Newtown, undated; 1 map (Box 6)
    - North Haven, 1960; 1 map (Box 6)
    - Norwalk, 1970, 1975; 3 maps (Box 6)
    - Norwich, 1976, 1978; 4 maps (Box 6)
    - Old Lyme, 1957, 1970; 3 maps (Box 6)
    - Oxford, 1964-1965, 1969; 13 maps (Box 6)
    - Plainfield, 1977, undated; 10 maps (Box 6)
    - Plymouth, 1959, undated; 12 maps (Box 7)
    - Portland, 1957, 1964-1965; 13 maps (Box 7)
    - Somers, 1948; 1 map (Box 7)
    - Sprague, undated; 1 maps (Box 7)
    - Stafford, undated; 1 map (Box 7)
    - Stamford, 1951,1961; 1 maps (Box 7)
    - Stratford, 1956, 1969; 2 maps (Box 7)
    - Suffield, undated; 1 map (Box 7)
    - Thomaston, 1955-1957, 1971, undated; 47 maps (Box 7)
    - Tolland, 1963-1964; 7 maps (Box 7)
    - Vernon, 1963, 1967 undated; 26 maps (Box 7)
    - Waterbury, undated; 9 maps (Box 7)
    - Watertown, 1943, 1955, 1964; 7 maps (Box 8)
    - Westbrook, 1960, undated; 3 maps (Box 8)
    - West Hartford, 1955, 1957, 1962; 4 maps (Box 8)
    - West Haven, 1967-1980, undated; 2 maps (Box 8)
    - Weston, 1957-1967, 1969, undated; 11 maps (Box 8)
    - Wethersfield, 1975 undated; 3 maps (Box 8)
    - Willimantic, 1964, 1972; 2 maps (Box 8)
    - Winchester, 1956; 2 maps (Box 8)
    - Windsor Locks, 1960; 1 map (Box 8)
    - Wolcott, 1962, undated; 7 maps (Box 8)
    - Woodbridge, undated; 15 maps (Box 8)
    - Woodstock, 1968; 11 maps (Box 8)
- Series 4. Office of Legal Assistance and Relocation, 1962-1984; 50 cubic feet
  These records are unarranged. The following is an initial box listing.
  - Appeals Files, 1962-1984; 1991-006; 50 cubic feet
    - Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 1)
    - Relocation, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
    - Contracts, 1976-1981 (Box 3)
    - Contracts, 1968-1983 (Box 4)
    - Appeals, 1968-1983 (Box 5)
    - Appeals, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 7)
    - Relocation, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
    - Relocation, 1971-1983 (Box 9)
    - Relocation, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
    - Relocation, 1978-1982 (Box 11)
    - Relocation, 1979-1981 (Box 12)
    - Relocation, 1979-1982 (Box 13)
    - Relocation, 1974-1981 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 15)
    - Contracts, 1976-1984 (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Relocation, 1980-1984 (Box 18)
    - Relocation, 1979-1982 (Box 19)
    - Contracts, 1978-1984 (Box 20)
    - Contracts, 1975-1980 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1986 (Box 22)
    - Relocation, 1971-1985 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1980 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 27)
    - Appeals, 1973-1985 (Box 28)
    - Legal Assistance, 1979-1981 (Box 29)
    - Legal Assistance, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
    - Relocation, 1979-1984 (Box 31)
    - Relocation, 1972-1984 (Box 32)
    - Relocation, 1973-1981 (Box 33)
    - Relocation, 1974-1979 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 36)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 37)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 43)
    - Relocation, 1970-1976 (Box 44)
    - Relocation, 1975-1977 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 47)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 48)
    - Corresopndence, 1962-1972 (Box 49)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 50)
    - Roll material, undated (Box 51)
    - Roll material, undated (Box 52)
- Series 5. Innovative Housing and Special Initiative Division, 1983-1989; 1 cubic foot
  - Director's Subject Files (T. Fusaro), 1983-1989; 1991-027; 1 cubic foot
    - COSCAA Housing Committee (Box 1)
    - Kensington Square, New Haven (Box 1)
    - Norwich, Martin House (Box 1)
    - T. Fusaro's weekly activity reports, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
    - Attorney General correspondence (Box 1)
    - Telephone log (Box 1)
    - Administrative Cost Program (Box 1)
    - Supervisor's meeting minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 1)
- Series 6. Policy and Planning Division, 1984; 1 cubic foot